BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 16) 6178/016
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 16)
1971- 1983
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United States Department of Labor
Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS)
6178/016
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Collective labor agreements.
5833678
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 30, 2005
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 21, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6178/001: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 1) 6178/002: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 2) 6178/003: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 3) 6178/004: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 4) 6178/006: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 6) 6178/007: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 7) 6178/008: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 8) 6178/009: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 9) 6178/010: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 10) 6178/011: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 11) 6178/012: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 12) 6178/013: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 13) 6178/014: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 14) 6178/015: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 15) 6178/017: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 17) 6178/018: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 18) 6178/019: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 19) 6178/020: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 20) 6178/021(d): BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 21) Digital 6178/022 mf: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 22) on Microfilm 6178/023: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 23)
Collective labor agreements - United States.; United States. Department of Labor. Bureau of Labor Statistics.
5833678
- Code no.551996: Otis Elevator Company and United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 989, 1974- 1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Code no.552001: Bethlehem Steel Corporation and Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America, Local 9, 1974- 1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Code no.552002: Standard-Thomson Corporation and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 274, 1974- 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Code no.552006: Kelsey-Hayes Company - Gunite Division and United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 718, 1974-1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Code no.552015: Celotex Corporation and United Paperworkers International Union, Local 307, 1976-1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Code no.552016: Midland-Ross Corp. and Surface Combustion Unit, Local 12, 1974-1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Code no.552022: Acco International Inc. and United Paperworkers International Union, Local 307, 1975-1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Code no.552039: Clark Equipment Company and United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 1290, 1974-1980 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Code no.552042: Dura Division, Dura Corporation and United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers, Local 16, 1974- 1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Code no.552050: Industrial Conference Board Locations of Tacoma, Washington and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge 297, 1974-1980 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Code no.552056: Painting and Decorating Contractors of the Springfield Area and International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades, Local 203, 1973-1979 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Code no.552057: Atlanta Newspapers and Atlanta Printing and Graphic Communications Union, N-101, 1974-1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Code no.552060: Evansville Contractors Association, Inc. and Lower Ohio Valley District Council of Carpenters, Locals 601,1341,694,1814, 1973-1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Code no.552061: American Sterilizer Company and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1974-1980 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Code no.552063: Airco Welding Products, Division Airco, Inc. and Phoenix Lodge No. 315, District 15, International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1974-1980 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Code no.552064: Cyanamid Company and International Chemical Workers Union, 1976-1980 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Code no.552067: Toledo Edison and Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 19, 1974-1979 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Code no.552071: Thatcher Plastic Packaging and International Chemical Workers Union, 1975-1980 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Code no.552074: Tilo Company, Inc. and United Steelworkers of America, 1971-1980 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Code no.552076: Koehring Company - Lorain Division and United Steelworkers of America, 1974-1980 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Code no.552081: Crown Cork and Seal Company and Sheet Metal Workers International Association, Local 172, 1973-1979 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Code no.552082: Menasco Manufacturing Company and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local 758, 1973- 1976 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Code no.552083: Lion Oil Company and International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 381, 1973-1979 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Code no.552084: Morgan Packing Company, Inc. and General Drivers, Warehousemen and Helpers, Local 89, 1974-1980 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Code no.552088: Borden, Inc. and Milk and Ice Cream Driver's and Dairy Employee's Union, Local 225, 1971-1977 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Code no.552089: B.F. Goodrich Chemical Company and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 4,228, 1975- 1979 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Code no.552115: Hawthorn Mellody Farms Dairy and Milk and Ice Cream Driver's and Dairy Employee's Union, Local 336, 1972- 1977 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Code no.552130: Lamson Division, Diebold, Inc. and Federal Labor Union Local 21664, 1976-1980 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Code no.552132: California Sheet Metal Employers and Sheet Metal Workers International Association, Local 272, 1974-1977 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Code no.552133: Ohio Barge Line, Inc. and National Maritime Union, 1973-1979 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Code no.552142: Sharon Steel Corporation and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 3-90, 1971-1980 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Code no.552143: Southwestern Portland Cement Co. and United Steelworkers of America, 1975-1981 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Code no.552147: Sunkist Growers and Teamsters Union Local 871, 1976-1980 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Code no.552148: Contractors of Jamesville, WI and United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry, Local 214, 1976-1980 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Code no.552150: C. Hager and Sons Hinge Manufacturing Company and United Steelworkers of America, Local 1509, 1974-1980 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Code no.552152: Litton Precision Gear and International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers-CLC, Local 1199, 1973- 1979 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Code no.552155: Indiana Desk Company, Inc. and United Furniture Workers of America, Local 334, 1973-1979 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Code no.552156: Caterpillar Tractor Co. and Allied Industrial Workers of America, Local 806, 1977-1983 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Code no.552004: McCord Corporation and Allied Industrial Workers of America, Local 616, 1974-1980 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Code no.552038: Clark Equipment Company and Allied Industrial Workers of America, Local 281, 1974-1980 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Code no.552053: Borg-Warner Corporation - Borg and Beck Division and United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 484, 1973-1979 (Box 1, Folder 41)